<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TfLiteImageClassification</string>
    <string name="description_info">Info</string>
    <string name="request_permission">This sample needs camera permission.</string>
    <string name="camera_error">This device doesn\'t support Camera2 API.</string>
    <string name="toggle_turn_on">NN:On</string>
    <string name="toggle_turn_off">NN:Off</string>
    <string name="toggle">Use NNAPI</string>
    <string name="tflite">tflite</string>
    <string name="nnapi">NNAPI</string>
    <string name="threads">Threads:</string>
<<<<<<< HEAD
    <string name="camera">Take a Photo</string>
=======

    <string name="InfoIntro">Learn about the Skin Conditions</string>
    <string name="BasalCell">Basal cell carcinoma: A type of skin
        cancer that begins with basal cells. This form typically
        appears as a flesh-coloured bump with transparent borders on the skin,
        sometimes with scars. The main cause is prolonged exposure to sunlight or UV rays.\n
        Source: <a href="https://dermatology.ca/public-patients/skin/basal-cell-carcinoma/">
            https://dermatology.ca/public-patients/skin/basal-cell-carcinoma
        </a></string>
    <string name="Melanoma">Melanoma: A type of skin cancer that
        occurs when the pigment producing cells that give colour
        to the skin become cancerous. The most dangerous form of
        skin cancer, these cancerous growths develop when skin cell
        DNA is damaged and trigger mutations. The main cause of melanoma is prolonged exposure
        to sunlight or UV rays. People who are fair-skinned, who gets sunburns easily or have a family
        history of melanoma are more likely to develop it.\n
        Source: <a href="https://dermatology.ca/public-patients/skin/melanoma/">
            https://dermatology.ca/public-patients/skin/melanoma
        </a></string>
    <string name="Keratosis">Actinic keratosis: A pre-cancerous area of thick,
        scaly, or crusty skin. These growths usually develop after prolonged exposure to sunlight
        or UV rays. They may develop into squamous cell carcinoma if left unchecked. People with
        Actinic keratosis are also likely to develop basal cell carcinoma and melanoma.\n
        Source: <a href="https://dermatology.ca/public-patients/skin/actinic-keratoses/">
            https://dermatology.ca/public-patients/skin/actinic-keratoses
        </a></string>
    <string name="Dermatofibroma">Dermatofibroma: A common benign fibrous nodule often
        arises on the skin of the lower leg. They are rarely painful and have no other ill effects
        Dermatofibroma lumps do not away on their own; they can be surgically removed.\n
        Source: <a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/a_to_z/dermatofibroma-a-to-z/">
            https://www.health.harvard.edu/a_to_z/dermatofibroma-a-to-z</a></string>
    <string name="Melanocytic">Melanocytic Nevi: More commonly known as a mole, these growths
        are composed of pigmented cells called melanocytes. They can be dark brown, yellow or
        flesh-coloured. The vast majority of moles that a person has appears during childhood
        and adolescence, though more may growth in adulthood. Most moles are benign, but some moles
        can be cancerous and may develop into melanoma. These moles are called dysplastic nevi. They
        are usually larger and more irregular than normal moles. They can be of mixed colours, are
        usually and irregular shape and grow noticeably over time.\n
        Source: <a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/a_to_z/moles-nevi-a-to-z/">
            https://www.health.harvard.edu/a_to_z/moles-nevi-a-to-z</a></string>
    <string name="Pyogenic">Pyogenic granulomas: These are non-cancerous skin growths that are small,
        round and usually blood red in color. They tend to bleed because they contain
        a large number of blood vessels. These skin growths mainly develop in
        children and young adults. The main cause is unknown, but they usually occur after
        an injury, and are easily infected. They can be surgically removed.
        Source: <a href="https://www.healthline.com/health/pyogenic-granuloma/">
            https://www.healthline.com/health/pyogenic-granuloma</a></string>
    <string name="Seborrheic">Seborrheic Keratoses: These are non-cancerous growths on the skin.
        They usually have an oily, crusty look, and can be tan, brown or black in colour.
        They are generally harmless, and are mostly found in the aging and elderly. They do not go
        away on their own. They can be surgically removed.
        Source: <a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/a_to_z/seborrheic-keratoses-a-to-z/">
            https://www.health.harvard.edu/a_to_z/seborrheic-keratoses-a-to-z</a></string>

>>>>>>> 935b6fe25160f51150a9c02ae10bfbac413b3185
    <string name="model">Model:</string>
    <string-array name="models">
        <item>Quantized</item>
        <item>Float</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="device">Device:</string>
    <string-array name="devices">
        <item>CPU</item>
        <item>GPU</item>
        <item>NNAPI</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
